ptemplates.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy - CubeCart Skins and Themes - PTemplates.com

Home > Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information, which is given by You to Us ("User Information") via PTemplates.com ("Website"). PTemplates.com have designed this Privacy Policy to increase Your confidence in PTemplates.com‘s guarantee that PTemplates.com will conform to all laws in order to ensure Your privacy and security without disclosing Your personal details.

All users of this Site are defined by the word “You/Your”. "We/Us/Our" means PTemplates.com and any member of Our entity and "Users" relate to the Users of Our Site either singularly or in plural form. PTemplates.com is dedicated to process personal information while adhering strictly to all Data Protection rules and regulations. 

###### Data Collection

Sometimes You will be compelled to submit User Information in order to participate in Our Site’s activity that includes games, competitions, message boards as well as shopping and video services. We guarantee that We will not disclose Your User Information and will only use it in compliance with Our Privacy Policy.

###### Our Usage of Your Data

Once you submit Your User Information, We hereby imply that You have read, understood and accepted our Privacy Policy which includes the fact that We have rights to retain Your User Information or any third party entity endorsed by Us.

We are allowed to use Your User Information for the following purposes:

  1. During market research where We will need to include statistical analysis of user behavior that consists of Your User Information. We may disclose this data to selected third parties.
  2. We may need Your User Information to assist with authorities as per required by the law.
  3. We require Your User Information so that we may communicate better with you via email in order to relate updated information concerning Our features, products and services, events and special offers. We will also include messages from third party companies or endorsed organizations. Should You choose to halt these communications, You may choose to do so by **clicking on the 'Unsubscribe' link provided in Our emails.**

Do note that We always take the initiative to gain Your permission if we were to disclose your personal information to third parties therefore enabling them to send you direct marketing information.

###### Cookies

We recommend that you take note of the fact that We hold the right to obtain User Information via Cookies which are miniscule text files that contain information concerning Your visits or name as an example. This will be done to optimise Our Site’s advertising. Do also note that in no way will Cookies act as viruses or infect Your files. Should You want to deter Us from User Information collection using Cookies, You may choose to disable Cookies in Your browser.

###### Security and Data Retention

We place the highest priority in security and may employ Secure Socket Layer (“SSL” encryption technology in order to safeguard Your payment and personal details.

###### Updates

You are recommended to contact Us in order to update or amend Your User Information when the need arises. We reserve the right to change Our Privacy Policy so it is recommended that You check Our Site regularly. Once You use Our Site it is automatically implied that You accept Our Privacy Policy. 

###### Contact

Should You feel the need to further understand Our Privacy Policy, please contact Us
